Yuri. Please go on a date with me.
侑里小姐，請跟我約會
I understand that things are busy right now, so once Valentine's Day ends,
公司現在很忙，所以等情人節結束後
I want to have a meal with you.
我想跟你一起吃飯
Yaksok.
“Yaksok”
Once Valentine's Day ends…
他說等情人節過後…
I wonder which day he meant.
具體來說是幾號？
This is so cute!
好可愛！
I've never heard of this game.
居然有這種遊戲
You feed your sea otter and raise it.
-要餵食，培育小海獺 -是喔
Huh? What's happening?
嗯？怎麼了？
It evolved!
牠進化了！
-Hooray!
-萬歲！
Looks like they're having fun.
他們好像聊得挺開心的
I'll be off.
-那我走了 -慢走
Stay safe.
-路上小心 -謝謝
All right.
好
Oh, Tae-o. Going somewhere?
哦，泰晤，你要去哪？
I'm helping at the Chocolat Festival.
我要去幫巧克力慶典
-Okay, good luck. -Thank you.
-這樣啊，有勞了 -好的
Yeah, good luck!
好，祝你順利！
I'll be off!
那我出發囉！
Yu… Boss.
侑…社長？
H-Hey.
你好啊
Have you eaten?
你吃飯了嗎？
Yeah.
吃了
-By the way… -Yes?
-我問一下… -什麼事？
About the promise…
約定你打算怎麼辦？
-We'll go. -Yeah, but…
-我會赴約 -是喔，但是…
Well, um…
我的意思是，那個…
When will we go?
要什麼時候去？
Are you perhaps busy on the night of Valentine's Day?
你情人節當晚忙不忙？
It's not that busy on the night of that day.
當天晚上應該不會太忙
So it's fine if we meet on the day of.
所以當天去也沒問題
Then I'd prefer Valentine's Day.
那我們情人節那天去吧
The 14th.
那就是14號
Yaksok.
約好了
What?
什麼？
Did you forget?
你忘了？
I haven't forgotten.
我沒忘記啦
Didn't I tell you to take notes so that you don't forget?
我不是總提醒你做筆記 以免忘了嗎？
My apologies, Boss.
抱歉，社長
-I'll be off, Boss. -Bye.
-我走了，社長 -路上小心
Things turned out great
多虧這束花
because of your flowers.
發生了非常棒的事
Thank you so much.
真的很謝謝你
Is that where you got the language of flowers idea from?
該不會花語的點子是來自這束花吧？
It's thanks to these flowers.
全都要多虧這束花
NOTICE MY LOVE FOR YOU
（請察覺我的愛意）
Are you getting on?
你不搭電梯？
Are you getting off?
你不下電梯？
-What? -Huh?
-什麼？ -怎樣？
Oh.
哦
Oh. Hmm.
哦，嗯
-Good morning. -Morning.
-早安
ALARM
（鬧鐘）
TAE-O
（泰晤）
Tonight is our Valentine's date.
今天晚上就是情人節約會囉！
Got it.
我知道了
READ
（已讀）
AMAZING!
（太棒了！）
Are you serious?
真的假的？
-Good morning.
-早啊 -早安
Good morning, Nishina. Have you eaten?
仁科小姐，早安，早餐吃了嗎？
Yeah, I did.
有，吃過了
Oh, by the way…
對了，話說回來…
He says that to everyone?
-他逢人都這麼說？ -泰晤，我下載了
-I downloaded the Rakkyun game. -Good morning.
-你昨天提到的小海獺遊戲 -大家早
Really?
-真的？有進化嗎？ -早安
Then I'll buy this one.
那我也挑這個
You have someone to give that too?
你有給巧克力的對象嗎？
Yes, I do.
嗯，有啊
No way. Who?
你騙人，是誰？
That's…
那個人是…
a secret.
秘密
Oh, right. The chocolate.
對耶，巧克力
Hanaoka!
花岡先生！
This is bad. The strawberries!
大事不妙，草莓出問題了！
What?
什麼問題？
They're late!
草莓好像不會送來！
What happened?
怎麼回事？
The ones for next week's dry fruit series?
不會是下週就要用在 果乾系列商品的草莓吧？
Yes, exactly!
對，就是那批草莓！
But production won't make it if they don't arrive today.
要是今天沒收到貨 到時會來不及生產
Yes, but the farm owner's wife collapsed and they've stopped harvesting.
對，我向農園確認情況 對方說太太病倒導致收成作業停滯
Well, the couple runs that small farm on their own.
畢竟那座小農園就靠他們夫妻在經營
How much have they harvested so far?
現階段收成多少草莓了？
Not sure.
這我不清楚，對方很著急 所以馬上就掛我電話
What do we do?
現在該怎麼辦？
Go to the factory and ask them for a production schedule change.
相原去工廠請對方變更生產時程
-Yes. -I'll go to the farm.
-是！ -我跑農園一趟
Right now? It's in Tochigi.
現在嗎？農園在栃木耶
-It's our fastest bet. -Okay.
-直接跑一趟最省時 -明白了
We might have to help harvest. Who else can come?
可能得幫忙採草莓 其他還有誰能去？
Nishina?
仁科小姐可以嗎？
Sorry, I have a PR meeting in the afternoon.
抱歉，我下午要開宣傳會議
Okay. Kame?
好，龜哥呢？
The Chocolat Fest ends today, so we have to tidy up.
今天是巧克力慶典最後一天 我得負責收尾
Oh, right.
說得也是
I'll go.
我去吧
Okay.
-好的 -真的假的？
No, I don't want both of us to be gone on Valentine's Day.
不行，今天是情人節 我不希望我們倆都不在公司
Right.
也對
What a relief.
真是萬幸
Then who else is free?
那其他有空的人…
Why are they all staring at me?
大家怎麼都盯著我看？
By the way,
那個…
what time will we get back by?
我們幾點能回去？
Depends on the situation,
得看情況而定
-but I think we can get back tonight. -Really?
-不過晚上應該能回去 -真的嗎？
That's great. I didn't know it was nearby.
太好了，農園離公司不遠啊
Oh, sorry. I'm sorry.
不好意思，抱歉
I'll get back by 7 p.m. Let's have dinner!
晚上七點前能回去 我們一起去吃飯吧！
A Valentine's date.
情人節約會
Chocolate!
巧克力！
What is she doing?
她是怎麼了？
Come here.
進來
Pardon my intrusion.
那我就打擾了
Was there an incident? An accident?
找我幹嘛？出事還是出意外了？
Thank you.
謝謝
Of course.
不客氣
Sorry.
抱歉
Thanks.
謝了
Are you hungry?
你肚子餓不餓？
Hm?
什麼？
A soft and chewy chocolate chip cookie.
我有充滿嚼勁的巧克力脆片餅乾
Oh.
哦
I avoid sugar around this time of the day.
我這個時段不太吃甜食
Is it good?
好吃嗎？
I guess.
還行
In Korea,
在韓國啊
this is how we feed kids who won't eat.
我們都這麼對付不吃飯的孩子
Is snow a rare sight for you?
你很少看到雪？
No, I'm sending it to the person I like.
不，我想拍下來傳給我喜歡的人
Oh, um…
哦，嗯…
I don't think…
我覺得啊…
she likes that kind of thing.
她應該不太喜歡那種事
"She"?
“她”？
It's Motomiya, right?
不就是本宮嗎？
-No. -Huh?
-不是她 -什麼？
Who is Motomiya?
本宮是誰？
Who could that be?
你說的是誰啊？
I don't understand Japanese.
我聽不懂日語
But…
可是…
You're having dinner together?
你們兩個要去吃飯？
That's your chance to give it to him.
那就一定要送巧克力呀
Right?
也是啦
It's a date on Valentine's Day, right?
你們是要在情人節當天約會吧？
-Yes. -It'd be crazy not to give him any then.
-對 -你若不送才顯得沒常識呢
You have no other choice.
你只有“送”這個選項
In fact, that's not where our main problem lies.
那不是該討論的重點
Where's our problem?
不然要討論什麼？
What chocolate are we giving him?
重點是你要送哪種巧克力給他
Oh, right.
也對啦
I think our Valentine's product would…
那還是送我們公司的情人節…
To someone who works here?
怎麼能拿自家產品送自家員工！
It's gotta be special.
你必須給他特殊待遇
Special?
特殊待遇？
After all, someone else might want to give Tae-o chocolate too.
畢竟想送泰晤巧克力的 不一定只有你一個
What?
什麼？
As for the Chocolat Festival…
巧克力慶典…
She might steal him away from you.
他可能會被人搶走喔
…we should raise them higher.
我希望能繼續拉抬
Is there anything Tae-o likes in particular,
泰晤有喜歡的東西嗎？
or something you'd like to give him?
或是你有沒有想送他什麼？
Linaria?
姬金魚草？
Okay, now I get it.
我懂了，原來是這麼一回事
You two were having a sneaky little romance.
你們倆居然在暗地裡你儂我儂
-No… -Well,
-沒有啦… -好吧
allow me to make something for you.
我親自幫你做
Chocolate with a top-quality taste and Linaria in the language of flowers.
幫你做個無敵美味的 姬金魚草花語巧克力
Are you sure?
你願意嗎？
Maybe I'll get someone to notice me too while I'm at it.
送我的意中人的話 他會不會發現我的心意呢？
LINARIA IN THE LANGUAGE OF FLOWERS
（姬金魚草的花語 請察覺我的愛意）
Who?
是指誰？
Oh, did you really find someone new?
啊，難道說你有新的對象了？
Bad news! Hanaoka might have found out about us!
不妙！花岡先生 可能發現我們倆的事了！
"Found out about us"?
“我們倆的事”？
TOBU TOCHIGI CENTRAL HOSPITAL
（東武栃木中央醫院）
Thank you.
謝謝
She's just slightly anemic.
夫人有輕微貧血的症狀
She hit her head when she fell, so they're running tests,
她暈倒時撞到頭部，目前正在檢查
but I'm glad it was nothing serious.
幸好沒有大問題
I see. That's a relief.
這樣啊，真是太好了
The harvest is almost done, so let's go now and help too.
草莓好像只剩一點就採完了 我們現在也去幫忙吧
-Okay. -But her tests aren't done.
-好的 -但我太太還在做檢查
I understand that you're worried,
我明白你心裡的擔憂
but it won't make much difference waiting here or at the farm.
不過在這等或是邊收成邊等結果 應該沒什麼差別
That's true.
說得也是
I'll stay with her then.
那我在這邊陪她
I'll be by her side.
我會陪在尊夫人身邊
Would that help?
這樣你能放心嗎？
Are you sure?
可以拜託你嗎？
Okay, then.
好的，來
Thank you.
謝謝
Thanks. I'll take care of things there.
謝謝，醫院這邊就交給你了
Okay.
好的
Thank you again.
拜託你了
Let's go.
-我們走吧 -好
Onoda, are you into sea slugs now?
小野田，你現在熱衷於研究海蛞蝓？
Yeah, since my black hagfish paper is going well.
因為黑黏盲鰻的論文 已經告一個段落了
Oh, I met the person Tae-o likes.
對了，泰晤有了喜歡的對象
This is our CEO and Mahiro.
她們是社長跟真尋小姐
Mahiro?
真尋小姐
Oh, what does she do?
話說她是做什麼的？
She's a co-worker.
是同一間公司的人
Tae-o likes someone from the same company, right?
泰晤喜歡的對象是他的同事沒錯吧？
Yes.
是啊
W-What was she like?
對方是什麼樣的人？
Well, she-
這個嘛，她是設…
"C"?!
“社”？
No, she--
不對，是設…
The CEO?! He can't!
-是社長嗎？不能是她！ -不
No, I'm not saying CEO!
不是！我是要講 “設計巧克力的人”！
What?
什麼？
She's a chocolatier.
對方是巧克力師傅
A chocolatier?
巧克力師傅？
She seems nice.
感覺人挺不錯的
Her chocolate was good.
巧克力也好吃
I see. A chocolatier.
這樣啊，是巧克力師傅
So, it's not the CEO, right?
所以不是社長就對了？
Yes.
對
Bravo!
好極了！
Sorry.
抱歉
The humidity went up.
激動之下影響到濕度了
MAHIRO IKEMOTO HAS SENT A MESSAGE
（池本真尋傳來訊息）
Hello, it's Mahiro Ikemoto.
我是池本真尋
I wanted to ask for your advice, Onoda.
其實我有件事想和小野田先生商量
Mahiro?
真尋？
What is it?
怎麼了？
Well, I got a text from the person Tae-o likes.
沒什麼，泰晤喜歡的對象聯絡我了
From the chocolatier?
是那個巧克力師傅？
I wonder…
這是…
What is this about?
怎麼回事？
There's no mistaking it.
絕對不會錯
She wants love advice from you, as she surely must like Tae-o as well.
她是來找你做戀愛諮詢的
So it's mutual?
所以是兩情相悅？
Of course it is.
想必是如此
With that lovable smile and personality,
他有可愛的笑容及可愛的性格
any living being would fall for a guy like that.
天底下沒有任何生物能不喜歡他
Then she should just tell Tae-o directly.
那她直接告訴泰晤不就好了？
I take back my bravo, Onoda.
那樣做一點都不好啊，小野田
She is an African crested porcupine.
她就像非洲冕豪豬
An African crested porcupine?
非洲冕豪豬？
The African crested porcupine is easily frightened
非洲冕豪豬是一種非常膽小的生物
and covers its whole body in quills to intimidate others.
所以會豎起全身的刺威嚇對手
Her back may be covered in sharp quills.
也許她背上滿是尖刺
So, give her a push from behind.
所以你試著溫柔地給她鼓勵
Gently.
推她一把
All right.
很好
I can spare some time if it's after 9 p.m. today.
若你今晚九點以後有空 我可以抽空和你見個面
9 p.m. on Valentine's Day?
情人節當天的晚上九點？
He's definitely interested.
他肯定對我有興趣
I got this in the bag.
簡直手到擒來
-I'll take it. -Okay.
-我來搬 -好
-Got it. -Thanks.
-來吧
This is the last.
搬完這籃就沒了
Thank you.
好的，謝謝
What time will you get to Tokyo?
預計幾點能送到東京？
I think I'll get there a bit past six.
晚上六點過後應該能送達
Got it.
我知道了
Thank you.
謝啦
Thanks for your help.
麻煩你了
I'm home, dear.
老公，我回來了
How were the tests?
檢查結果怎麼樣？
They were all good.
沒有問題
I just need some rest.
醫生說多休息就沒事了
Really? What a relief.
是嗎？那真是萬幸
Thank you so much.
真的很感謝你
I'm glad it was all okay.
真替兩位高興
I'm sorry for the trouble.
-給你們添麻煩了 -沒有啦
The shipment went out okay.
草莓都順利出貨了
We'll be leaving now.
那我們就先告辭了
Please take care.
請夫人保重身體
Goodbye.
再見
Excuse me.
請留步
I'd like to thank you somehow.
請讓我們聊表一下感謝之情
It's fine.
沒關係啦
Please stay for dinner.
吃過晚餐再走吧
No, dinner is--
不用了，晚飯…
-Just stay the night. -What?
-難得來一趟，住一晚再走吧 -什麼？
I can't stay the night. I need to return by seven.
不能留宿，我得在七點前回去
Do you have plans?
你有約了嗎？
Well…
也不是…
Of course he does. It's Valentine's Day.
肯定有啊，今天可是情人節
No.
不是的
Of course, a great guy like him would have a date on Valentine's.
這樣的大帥哥情人節一定有約了
No, I don't have any plans today.
你們誤會了，我沒有什麼安排
We'll stay over.
我們就住一晚吧
Please, come in then.
-那兩位請進 -請進…
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
（什麼意思？ 他絕對發現了！）
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
（出了什麼事？）
HANAOKA
（花岡）
Hello?
喂？
The strawberries were sent out.
草莓順利出貨了
Oh, what a relief. Thanks, got it.
天啊，太好了 非常感謝你們，我明白了
And we're staying here tonight.
還有啊，我們要在這留宿一晚
Oh… What? Staying there?
是喔…什麼？你們要留宿？
Tae-o too.
泰晤也要和我一起住下來
Oh, um… I see.
是喔，這樣啊，知道了
So, um…
那你們…
Bye then.
總之就是這樣
Wait a sec--
你別掛…
Yes?
請進
Boss, is Tae-o coming back today?
社長，泰晤今天會回來嗎？
What?
什麼？
Oh, I just got a call saying they won't make it back today.
其實啊，我剛接到通知 他們今天回不來
Does that mean you got a call from Tae-o?
接到通知？是泰晤聯絡你？
No, it was from Hanaoka.
不是他，是花岡
Really?
這樣啊
Understood.
我知道了
All done.
吃得一乾二淨呢
Put that down.
你別弄了…
But…
可是…
I'll do it, so hurry to bed now.
我來收拾就好，你今天早點休息
Yes, okay.
好啦…
I'll carry it.
那我拿過去
-Sorry. -Thank you.
-抱歉喔 -謝謝
Over here.
跟我來
FATE
（純米吟釀）
I'm sorry about today.
今天真是抱歉
Since you're here, let's drink up.
來都來了，喝一杯吧
Hanaoka can't drink alcohol.
花岡先生不喝酒
I can't drink today either.
我今天也不喝
Oh, really? Then…
是喔，那麼…
You two can have some tea.
來，你們兩位就喝茶吧
Thank you.
謝謝你
Here you go.
請喝
Tae-o.
泰晤
My bad.
對不起啦
I'm always so cold to you.
老是對你冷言冷語
Can you really get this drunk from that?
只是那樣就醉了？
And yet…
誰叫我…
I don't have any charm in my arsenal.
天生親和力就是零
My bad.
對不起啦
Sir.
伯父
Yes?
怎麼了？
Even though you were worried about your wife,
在你放心不下夫人的時候
We sincerely apologize.
真的萬分抱歉
What happened to "My bad"?
怎麼不說“對不起啦”？
You're such a cute, kind little guy.
泰晤是個可愛的好孩子
And yet I'm…
但是我卻…
I forgive you, so please sleep.
我原諒你，快睡吧
Listen up, Tae-o.
你聽好，泰晤
You're a good kid.
你是好孩子
But you know…
不過…
Even so,
她卻不一定
that doesn't mean she'll see you in a romantic way.
會因此視你為戀愛對象
What do you mean?
你這話是什麼意思？
I feel sorry for you.
為你感到可惜啊
The person you like…
你所喜歡的那個人…
When it comes to love…
對愛情…
My bad.
對不起啦
He's sleeping too?
大叔也睡了？
Hanaoka? Hey.
花岡先生？醒醒啊
Yuri.
侑里
Oh, sorry, what was that?
啊，抱歉，你說什麼？
Congratulations on finishing Valentine's Day.
情人節辛苦你了
You seem tired.
你看起來很累
Yeah, I really am.
對啊，累死了
Did something happen at work?
工作上有什麼問題嗎？
No.
沒有
Oh, or could it be you actually found someone you like?
啊，還是說你 真的有喜歡的對象了？
I haven't.
沒有
I haven't found anyone.
我沒有喜歡的人
You're perceptive of others' feelings,
你雖然對別人內心的想法很敏銳
but you don't understand your own very well.
卻遲遲無法察覺自己真正的心情呢
Or are you resisting them?
或者說你是在抗拒？
What am I resisting?
抗拒什麼？
Your true feelings.
抗拒自己真實的心情
He's Dr. Onoda.
他是小野田博士
Doctor?
“博士”…
For a doctor, don't look unattainable. Be approachable.
跟博士約會，穿平易近人的低跟鞋 比當高不可攀的花朵更好
For a doctor, don't do high-class glamor. Look natural and ephemeral.
跟博士約會，自帶天然嬌弱感的妝容 比有高級感的妝更好
For a doctor, even while being ephemeral, show you have a strong will.
跟博士約會，得把自己塑造成 嬌弱卻心懷堅定意志的女性
Now then, let's go snatch a doctor.
該去拿下醫學博士了
Welcome.
歡迎光臨
Sorry for being late.
抱歉，我來遲了
It's okay. I understand.
沒關係，我能理解
You're in a busy line of work.
你這職業就是忙嘛
Oh, what would you like?
對了，你要點什麼？
Water, please.
白開水
Water?
白開水？
I can't drink. I'm still working.
我還有工作，今天不能喝酒
Sorry, I'd like some water.
不好意思，請給我一杯水
Yes, sir.
好的
It's okay. I understand.
沒關係，我能理解
You never know when you'll be called in for work.
你這職業得24小時待命嘛
Here.
請用
What kind of doctor are you, Onoda?
小野田先生是哪個科系的博士？
The marine life department.
我是海洋生物科博士
Is that a thing?
有那種科系啊？
Yes.
有啊
You wanted advice?
所以你想找我商量什麼？
Oh, let's see…
這個嘛，我想想…
Actually, my heart has been pounding recently.
其實我最近有時會心悸
Pounding?
心悸？
Intensely?
頻脈嗎？
Or is your heart fluttering?
感覺心臟跳很快？
Yes, sort of like that.
對，大概是那種感覺
I see.
原來如此
She's hiding her true feelings.
她隱藏了自己的真心
That's a trait that only exists in humans and not animals.
動物做不到那點 這是人類獨有的特質
But she has no need to hide those feelings.
但那樣的真心話不需要隱藏
Do you know why?
你知道原因嗎？
Because their feelings are mutual.
因為他們倆互相喜歡
Onoda.
小野田
Your job is to casually make sure
你的任務就是若無其事地
that they realize this fact.
讓她意識到這一點
It's okay.
不用擔心
The heart belongs to you,
你的內心
more than you may believe.
比你想像得更忠於自己
The heart? My actual heart?
內心？你是指心臟？
You should try facing it head-on.
我建議你放開手腳去嘗試
That kind of treatment exists?
還有那種治療法？
You don't need treatment.
你不需要治療
That fluttering isn't an illness.
你的心搏過速不是病
Quills?
尖刺？
Are you trying to say
是不是代表
that my feelings will be accepted?
我的心意會被對方接受？
I'm sure of it.
一定會的
You're sure?
一定會嗎？
Do you understand?
可以了嗎？
Oh, yes.
啊，可以
It's time for me to go.
我該走了
Wait, what?
等等，什麼？
After all, it's a full moon.
畢竟今天是滿月
Excuse me.
稍等一下
Take this as a thank you for today.
這個送你，謝謝你今天來一趟
Are you sure? I love your chocolate. This is great.
可以收下嗎？ 我很喜歡你做的巧克力，真開心
It's linaria chocolate I made just for today, not meant for sale.
這是我特製的姬金魚草巧克力 是非賣品喔
Please look up what it means in the language of flowers.
請你查查看花語
Don't you know?
你不知道？
What?
什麼？
I know what it means.
我知道呀
Yet you won't tell me what it is?
你知道卻不告訴我？
Huh?
什麼？
Oh, um…
這個嘛…
Please notice
“請察覺…
my love for you.
我的愛意”
Don't worry. I'm sure it's been noticed.
放心吧，對方一定發現了
Now then, please watch over Tae-o.
那就麻煩你多關照泰晤了
What?
什麼？
WHAT HAPPENED? I HEARD YOU'RE STAYING THE NIGHT
（出了什麼事？聽說你們要留宿 看來今天是約不成了）
READ
（已讀）
YUN TAE-O
（尹泰晤）
Hello?
喂？
I broke our promise.
沒能履行約定
My bad.
對不起啦
It is what it is.
你也是迫於無奈
I couldn't reply either.
連訊息都沒辦法回
My bad.
對不起啦
More importantly, are things okay with Hanaoka?
這不重要，花岡還好嗎？
I'm not sure, but he's drunk right now.
不清楚，他現在喝醉了
What? Drunk?
什麼？喝醉？
Sorry, hold on.
抱歉，等我一下
Open up, Yuri.
侑里小姐，麻煩開個門
What?
什麼？
Weren't you staying the night?
怎麼回來了？不是要留宿嗎？
I made a promise.
我們約好了嘛
But we didn't get to have dinner. My bad.
不過沒能去吃飯，對不起啦
Why do you keep talking like that?
幹嘛？你從剛才 講話方式怎麼怪腔怪調的？
Have some strawberries. They were a gift.
這是人家送我的草莓，請你吃
Oh.
好
They look tasty. Thanks.
感覺很好吃，謝謝你
Well then, good night.
那就晚安囉
What? You're leaving already?
什麼？你要回去了？
Are you lonely?
捨不得我走？
Of course…
不是啦
I'm sure you're lonely, but Hanaoka is sleeping right outside.
我想你會寂寞 但花岡先生還在車上睡覺
Oh, then you should go quickly.
什麼？那你馬上回去吧
Dream about me.
夢見我吧…
What?
這是做什麼？
I cast a spell.
我施了魔法
Dream about me, okay?
要夢到我喔
I'm sorry, I won't anymore.
抱歉，我不會再夢到你了
Have a good night then.
那就晚安囉
Wait.
等等
No, it's nothing.
算了，沒事
Thanks.
謝謝你的草莓
Sleep tight.
晚安
Tae-o.
泰晤
Here.
給你
"Joa"?
“Joa”？
Good morning.
早安
Joa haeyo means "Do you like me?" in Korean.
“Joa haeyo”這句話的意思是 “你喜歡我嗎？”
He said "like."
他說“喜歡”
What do I do?
怎麼辦？
Yes?
請進
Oh, right.
啊
Good work on your business trip.
謝謝你願意出差，辛苦了
Thanks.
不客氣
Hey--
那個…
The wife's condition seemed fine,
夫人的身體狀況還不錯
so their future shipments should be fine.
未來交貨應該不會出問題
I see.
這樣啊
That's great.
太好了
Thanks.
謝謝你
That Valentine gift isn't for someone special, right?
你不是不看重情人節的嗎？
Well, we work with chocolates.
我畢竟是做這行的嘛
No, that's not what I meant.
不，我不是那個意思
Did you have Mahiro make those?
那是你叫真尋做的？
Oh, um…
哦，那是…
Don't abuse your power too much.
濫用職權請適可而止
It's not like that.
我沒有濫用職權
You're not like yourself lately, Motomiya.
你最近有些不尋常
How so?
哪裡不尋常了？
You're not influenced by emotion.
你這個人不會輕易受感情影響
That's why I trust you.
正因為你為人如此 我才會對你深信不疑
And the company--
公司…
I know.
我知道
I know that better than anyone.
我自己最清楚
If you say so.
那就好
Can we go on a date today?
今天可以約會嗎？
You haven't dated anyone since high school?
你高中畢業後就沒跟任何人交往過？
Or I guess you could say
說高中畢業後不太貼切
that guy was my first and last boyfriend.
當時那個人是我第一個 也是最後一個交往對象
He's your last one?
最後一個？
I don't plan on dating anyone anymore.
我不打算再跟任何人談戀愛了
I bet he cheated on you. Tell me.
他鐵定劈腿了，說嘛
Let's stop talking about me.
-我的事怎樣都好，別說了 -他是什麼樣的男人？
I thought you weren't going to date anymore.
她不是不打算談戀愛了嗎？
You're not like yourself lately, Motomiya.
你最近有些不尋常
You're not influenced by emotion.
你這個人不會輕易受感情影響
Yuri!
侑里小姐！
Thank you.
謝謝
Sorry to interrupt.
打擾了
Let's eat.
我開動了
Enjoy.
好好享用
Um, has Hanaoka noticed anything?
請問一下，花岡先生果然發現了吧？
No, don't worry about it, Tae-o.
沒有啦，沒事，你不用擔心
Really?
這樣啊
Yes. Let's focus on the food. Time to eat.
對，吃飯吧，我開動了
You're as pretty as always today.
你今天一樣可愛
Yesterday,
昨天啊
when I wasn't around, what were you up to?
我不在的期間，你做了什麼？
What was I up to? The same as always.
做了什麼？就跟平常一樣
I worked.
工作
Right, you worked as always. What else?
是喔，跟平常一樣工作，還有呢？
And I chatted with Mahiro.
還跟真尋聊了一下
I see. You chatted with Mahiro. What else?
這樣啊，跟真尋小姐聊了一下 還有呢？
Actually, I think Mahiro found someone she likes.
說到真尋，她好像有喜歡的人了
And how about you?
那你呢？
Have you found someone you like?
你沒有喜歡的人嗎？
I missed you while we were apart, Yuri.
和你分開時，我很想你，侑里小姐
While we were apart,
你在我們見不到面的期間
did you somehow become cuter?
變得更可愛了嗎？
What's the matter?
怎麼了？
I got too embarrassed.
我有點招架不住
Thank you.
謝謝你
Is the food good?
菜色好吃嗎？
Yes, it's delicious.
超好吃的
And what a lovely restaurant.
而且這間餐廳也很棒
Nishina told me about it.
這間餐廳是仁科小姐告訴我的
What?
什麼？
I see.
這樣啊
Nishina told you?
她告訴你的啊？
I…
是喔
I see.
原來如此
It's okay.
儘管放心
Nishina is my senpai.
我只把仁科小姐視作職場前輩
That's all.
僅此而已
I wasn't--
我沒放在心上…
And Nishina is in a relationship.
況且仁科小姐有男朋友了
Like I said…
都說了…
-What? She's in a relationship? -Yes.
-什麼？她有男朋友？ -對
She told me
她說他們兩個
they've been dating since high school.
從高中時期就開始交往了
That's so long.
好久啊
Wait, then what about that chocolate?
等等，既然如此 那份巧克力是怎樣？
They were for her co-workers. Everyone got some.
是人情巧克力，大家都有收到
Okay, I see now.
原來是這樣，了解
Could it be that you're jealous?
那個，你吃醋了？
No.
我沒有
Then why does it bother you?
不然你為什麼會介意？
Huh?
什麼？
Forget about it.
沒什麼
I'm going to the restroom.
我去趟洗手間
"Nareul joa hani kka"?
“Nareul joa hani kka”？
No, I shouldn't.
不行，唯有這件事不能做
You're perceptive of others' feelings,
你雖然對別人內心的想法很敏銳
but you don't understand your own very well.
卻遲遲無法察覺自己真正的心情呢
Or are you resisting them?
或者說你是在抗拒？
Your true feelings.
抗拒自己真實的心情
-"Twinkle Twinkle Little Star"? -Yes.
-你在唱《小星星》？ -對
Seeing the stars makes me want to sing.
當我看見星星就想唱
I don't see any.
但我沒看到星星耶
Jeez.
天哪
-Yuri. -Yes.
-侑里小姐 -怎麼了？
This is when it gets romantic.
現在得營造浪漫氣氛
It's called reading the room.
這就叫“看氣氛”
Oh, right.
哦
Sorry.
對不起
I guess I have no choice.
真拿你沒辦法
That's…
那是…
Yes, I got it at the restaurant earlier.
我剛剛在餐廳拿到的
I already know
我早就明白…
why I get jealous over him…
自己會忍不住吃醋的原因
and the reason why I want to know his inner thoughts.
以及想瞭解泰晤心中想法的理由
It's gotten romantic now, hasn't it?
氣氛浪漫起來了，對吧？
Well, then.
來吧
I can't resist anymore.
我再也無法抗拒了
I…
我…
like…
就是喜歡…
this man.
這個人
Tae-o.
泰晤
Here.
這給你
For me?
送我的？
Bye.
那我走囉
Yuri.
侑里小姐
Big Sis!
大姐姐！
Big Sis, read me more of that picture book.
大姐姐，繼續讀繪本給我聽
Sure.
好啊
"When she locks eyes with another, only then can she hear
“那個能力就是在互相對望時
the voice in their heart."
她可以聽到對方的心聲
"One day, the girl met a boy with a kind heart."
有天少女遇見了少年 他擁有一顆溫柔的心
"The boy showed a great amount of love to the girl."
少年向少女傳達了許多愛意”
Subtitle translation by: Chul Woong Kim
字幕翻譯：劉維容
Is Hanaoka special to you?
花岡先生是特別的嗎？
Is that okay, Motomiya?
本宮，你能接受？
Do you want to date him?
侑里小姐，你想和他交往嗎？
There's no rule against dating co-workers.
公司並未明令禁止辦公室戀情
I had no idea this entire time.
我一直都不知道
Saranghae.
Saranghae
I've always loved you.
我從很久以前就喜歡你了